signing to dive into.
>> This confus continues to evolve as the
season goes on.
>> Welcome into Bucks Insider presented by
Hard Rock Vet Sports Book. Casey
Phillips, Scott Smith, and Brie Dixs
here for you. And just when you think
we're done with free agency,
>> we're not done.
>> Just another wave. We just keep on
rolling through, signing a few new
people, a few new old people, per se. Uh
people that it's not their first stint
with the Buccaneers, which we always
love. Love a guy circling back. So, uh,
let's talk a little bit about this
second wave of free agency and who we
have brought in and brought back. Uh,
who did you want to highlight?
>> Yeah, I think this is kind of a common
thing. It's that that second wave is
usually just a little bit before the
draft. I think you're just shoring up a
few positions that helps you be
>> able to move any direction you want to
in the draft. Uh, the guy I want to talk
about, the Bucks brought back Justin
School, the swing tackle that was here
from 2022 to 2024. I honestly don't
think the Bucks wanted him to leave last
year in Fregency. I think they were a
little unhappy that they didn't get that
deal done. So, um, they bring him back
after one year and a good year for him
in Minnesota. He started nine games for
the Vikings. So, he ended up being kind
of important for them. Uh, seven at
right tackle, seven at left tackle, two
at right tackle. Uh, prior to that, he
had started five games in 2024 for the
Bucks at both right and left tackle. So,
he's that classic swing tackle that you
feel good about being able to plug in on
either side. And as we saw the last two
years, as great as our tackle duo is of
Tristan Worse and Luke Etek, both guys
miss a little time in the last couple
years. So, it's good to have and we have
Benjamin Chuck Wuma who was great as a
rookie, but it's always good to have
more depth there at, you know, more at
the very important tackle position.
>> Yeah, that's true. And then, uh, one
person we brought back that isn't isn't
a person who's been here before, one
kind of new in this second wave
addition. Tell us who that is.
>> Brought in David SS from the Falcons,
which he had one of the best years of
his career last year. had a good game
against the Bucks in December. Had, I
think, six receptions, 78 yards, but
really a big receiver, friendly target
for Baker Mayfield. Great in those 50/50
balls, slants, fades. So, I'm excited to
see what he's able to bring to the Bucks
receiving court.
>> So, he's our Mike Evans replacement.
>> Yes. Basically kind of has that longsted
buildup speed.
>> No, no, no, no. I was making a joke.
That's absolutely not the way we should
react to any receiver side
>> ever. Ever. No, never never anybody to
trying to replace my game.
>> Sets them up for failure. Uh yeah, I I
think good depth.
>> He is the guy who uh broke our hearts in
that game on that fourth down
conversion. We don't need to talk about
it, but I just want to say, look, if uh
we don't want it to happen again, we're
just like, cool, come join our team.
>> And I think it's, you know, you you joke
about the guy Zack Robinson and bringing
in a guy from the Falcons, but I think
that is kind of that means he he knows
him. He knows what he can do. Um he
probably put in a good word, I would
imagine.
>> Yep. And then our other addition uh that
was here before, Rake Nunees Roches. Let
me tell you the excitement.
>> Also known as
>> Nacho. And first of all, that's already
worth it right there. Uh second of all,
I my husband can vouch. The moment I
found this out in our house, he heard me
yell, "Let's go
>> because
>> I think you did that via text as well."
>> I did. I actually did send that in text
as well. That was my sentiment with him
because he's just so fun. He is the He
is so much energy. And let me tell you
how loud this man is at practice, in the
huddle, there is no off switch.
>> And I feel like in the doldrums of the
season, week 13, 14, you know, you need
a guy like this. I mean, look at him.
You can't I mean, you can't not be fired
up about this. And outside of the
energy, he has had some great years
here. Has had a great year with the
Giants at one point where he had a a
careerhigh in sacks. and um he was here
for five seasons before with us. Started
15 different games at nose tackle,
playoffs included, and started in the
Super Bowl. Um I just think he's a great
addition where we did need a little more
Dline depth. You know, when you lost to
Logan How and now you have Aan Robinson,
you have him. I think you feel a little
bit better about your your depth overall
at defensive line going into the draft,
which is great. And again, just a a a
huge energy guy that really, especially
at practice, keeps everyone very
engaged, very hype, may or may not start
some stuff, you know, that's just that's
that's his vibe. So happy to have him
back.
>> Vita, Kalija Cany, Aan Robinson, not not
Rake Nunes ro that's especially because
he's coach Bull said he wanted to get
bigger.
>> Yep. Bulking up.
>> Yeah, that's a pretty good That's a
pretty good rotation right there.
>> I would agree with that for sure. All
right, so now we are nearing the
offseason program actually starting. Um
it it this is always just a great time
of year. We're finally going to have
some guys back in the building, but it
looks a little different as it goes
through, right? It's there's phases,
there's different aspects to it. So, um
it will begin Monday, April 20th is the
official beginning of the offseason
program. Lasts for nine weeks and
concludes with a full team mandatory
mini camp from June 16th to 18th. So,
wanted to kind of highlight this as
we're about to get in it for everybody
to know what to expect to see out of
some of our coverage here, what is and
is not going to be happening on the
practice field in the weight room. So,
um, that's kind of how long it runs and
figured we'd get into again the phases a
little bit to remind people what that
looks like.
>> Yeah, there's three phases. This is this
is mandated by the NFL. You have to
follow these rules that's been
negotiated in various CBAs over the
years. Um, it's nine weeks in total. The
first two weeks are phase one. And in
that, you can have meetings, although
only a certain amount. You can only meet
for a certain number of hours a day. And
then all the onfield work is just
strength and conditioning. The only
coaches that can be on the field with
the players on those first two weeks are
strength and condition coaches. Then you
move to phase two
>> uh where you can have the other
assistant coaches on the field and you
can run drills, but they can't be
offense against defense. It's it's, you
know, individual position drills, that
sort of thing. Then you get to phase
three, that lasts three weeks. Then you
get to phase three and now you're seeing
practices, we call them organized team
team activity days or OTAAS where that
look like what you'd expect a practice
to look like. You can have seven on
seven, you can have nine on seven, you
can have full team 11 on 111 drills.
Still no pads, no contact, but it it
looks like an actual practice. And you
get up to 10 of those over the course of
a 3-week period.
>> And then of course, as you said, the
mandatory mini camp at the end caps the
whole thing, right?
>> So,
>> yeah.
>> Well, and almost pretty much voluntary
until you get up to the mandatory mini
camp, but the Bucks typically have
really good attendance kind of in all
phases, guys trying to gel, gain
camaraderie. Um, so good to see who's
all out there. Sure. Yeah.
>> Yeah. We I think the weather has
something to do with it and people like
being down here in Tampa at this time of
year. So that
>> getting acclimated.
>> I always think it's funny when I I'll
talk to guys like, "Oh, where are you
going to spend the off season?" And
January, February, they're like, "Oh,
I'm going up north to Pittsburgh." And
I'm like, "No, no, no. You You've done
this wrong. This is when you want to be
here."
>> They're like, "Yeah, I'll come back in
August." I'm like, "You've really you
are doing this the wrong way."
>> I would say it got a little cold this
this year.
>> That's I Yeah, we are so weak for saying
that. Anyone who is a Bucks fan that's
watching this from up north is like, "Oh
my god, that's in the 60s."
>> 22-year-old me from St. Louis would be
so mad at at me now.
>> Yeah. You'd be like, "Man, what a wuss
we've all turned out to be after just a
few winters here. It's all it takes."
Uh, all right. So, also we of course
it's mockdraft season, right? That's
what everybody loves doing. That's what
everybody here loves doing. I know.
>> Bri, I know for a fact
favorite thing to do in the whole world.
So we figured as we are getting close,
we are just a few weeks away now and
wanted to see kind of what the the mock
drafts are saying, what you guys are
saying at this point. So uh tell me a
little bit about your each of your most
recent mock drafts.
>> Mary's going to go first, but let me
explain that each of us in our last two
mockdrafts instead of doing a pick all
the picks in the first round, we picked
all the Bucks and to fill in the gap, we
used the gaps, we used a mockdraft
simulators. So you couldn't go like,
"Oh, we're going to get, you know, Sunny
Styles in the first round and Ruben Bane
in the second round." It had to be
realistic.
>> No way.
>> So all the picks were filled in and then
you made their picks and and in my case,
I'll get to it, but you can also it also
sometimes offers you trades. So you
>> So in the first round I had the Bucks
taking edge, Hakee Meador, who he is 25
years old, but he also, in my opinion,
has one of the best pass rush arsenals
and rush plans of the entire class. um
is a guy that was in the top 10 in the
power four in pass win rate. But to me,
he's a guy that he can win with power,
he can win with finesse. And a lot of
the things I think that I initially said
about Kijiji Hansy coming out was the
pass rush sequence, being able to kind
of stack moves together. And he doesn't
just rely on athleticism, he also wins
with effort, with a feel for blockers.
So, I'm excited to see what where he
goes. is um he's kind of a little bit
all over Mox a little bit at this point.
So, we'll see if he would be there at
15. And then in the second round, I had
the Bucks taking Texas Tech linebacker
Jacob Rodriguez, who has a very rare
transition from quarterback to
linebacker. So, you see that in
>> What are you talking about? That's a
very typical type of pipeline. Who
doesn't make that transition?
>> Has um incredible lad lateral quickness,
the range. He reached the top speed of
over 18 miles an hour during the
backpedal and react drill at the
combine. The fastest by any linebacker
over the last four years, finished fifth
in Heisman voting. Has pretty much every
accolade in his trophy case.
>> Um is a guy that can quickly accelerate,
get from point A to point B. Um had has
mastered the art of the peanut punch,
similar to what we've seen from Levante
David. had seven force fumbles in 2025
and then ranks top 10 in FBS history in
career force fumbles. Great awareness on
the field. And then in the third round I
had the Bucks taking defensive tackle
Grayson Halton from Oklahoma that is
just an absolute tree trunk is a guy
that wins with quickness.
>> Is there any award that Jacob Rodriguez
didn't win?
>> Apparently not.
>> He was fifth in high school.
>> I don't think so.
I think he won a Nobel Peace Prize,
>> a daytime Emmy.
>> Yeah, he's got everything. Also, I
learned real quick, this is going to
sound very random, but while she said
this, it made me think of it. When I
used to work in radio, they would
sometimes have us do like tongue
twisters before we went on, almost like
as a warm-up. I decided the new Yeah.
The pass rush win rate is what I've
decided is our new one to say because I
know for me it will turn into pass win
rate. Yes. Which is pretty much what I
just said.
>> So, I'm like I I've heard I'm like that
is a hard one to say. Anyways, carry on.
>> Yes. Um,
>> so I'll take I'll take your um Hakee
Messor in the first round and raise you
Messtor.
>> I thought you said this was a realistic.
>> It was offered to me. The draft the
trade was offered to me from Cleveland.
I'm like, "Yes, I'll take that." Moving
down from 15 to 24 and picking up 39.
So, I ended up This was great. I I I
will admit I then tried to run it with
the same draft simulator multiple more
times. They would not give me that deal
again. So, it was a onetime thing.
>> So, we're just going to hope Cleveland
>> Cleveland maybe lost their mind a little
bit, but I do think it's realistic to
trade down and get something in the
second or third round, but this is what
I got. So, an extra third round pick.
I'm not going to go through the whole
Akeem messador scattering report cuz Bri
already handled that very well. But I
also he was still on the board for me at
24. So, that's a win. That's a win. And
then in 39 and 46, I didn't have to
choose between quarterback and
linebacker, which I think uh quarterback
is kind of a sneaky need for the Bucks.
And everybody knows we need linebacker.
I got Colton Hood, very productive guy,
very sticky, very good in coverage, a
physical style of play, good wingspan, I
think the kind of quarterback we like.
And then I got Anthony Hill of Texas.
Um, maybe not as proficient in coverage
as Jacob Rodriguez. He really wasn't
asked to do a lot in coverage by Texas,
but he's a he's a very good runto
stopper with good size. Uh, and then in
the third round, I took Keelin Rutled, a
guard from Georgia Tech, and I'm not
being a homer with the Georgia Tech pick
there. This is a guy who's very much a a
tone setter on the field that which we
like from our offensive lineman. He
would fit right in with guys like Cody
Mal and and before him Ryan Jensen and
Luke Geti. Um just hard-nosed guys, big
uh moves quickly laterally. I know we
have two starting guards, Cody Malc and
Ben Benesen, but both those guys are
contracts are up by 2027. And it's
always good to think about the future
and think about depth. So, uh, at that
very fortunate trade offer to me, I
think helped me fill a lot of needs in
the first three rounds.
>> I also just want to make sure I say
this. So, we've had to hear about
Northwestern from you for years, and now
because of your son, we also are going
to have to hear about Georgia Tech. Just
wanted to
>> My dad went to Oklahoma, too, so I'm
going to claim any Oklahoma.
>> We're going to claim any of those
people. We're just Anyone else want to
say that they're part of Scott's family?
Claim all the names. All right, that's
>> my sister went to Missou.
>> I'm I've already got that one covered.
So, me and your sister, we can we can
sell.
>> And they don't have a football team at
our college. Oh, so sad. Yeah. All
right. Well, that's going to do it for
us on this edition of Bucks Insider.
Thanks so much for being with us, and
we'll see you next time.